J. D. Sloan Photographs MS247
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic prints and negatives, 1978 -- 2013; MS247.001; 7.4 Linear Feet
  - Tufts 1996 Volume 2, MS247.001.004.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Tufts Club Bostonian: Annual Freebie, 1996-10-08; MS247.001.004.00002.00002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      961008-A to 961008-C
      Elaine Garrity
    - Tufts Chemistry Pearson Rededication, 1996-05-17; MS247.001.004.00002.00003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960517-A to 960517-E
    - Tufts Dental International Students Commencement, 1996-11-15; MS247.001.004.00002.00004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      961115-A to 961115-F
    - Tufts Dental International Students Commencement, 1996-11-15; MS247.001.004.00002.00005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      contact sheets; Boston Campus
    - Tufts Dental Wide Open, 1996-10-07; MS247.001.004.00002.00006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      961007-A to 961007-L
    - Tufts Dental Lloyd Miller, 1996-10-24; MS247.001.004.00002.00007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      961024-A to 961024-E
    - Dental Family Day, 1996-03-29; MS247.001.004.00002.00008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960329-A to 960329-C
    - Tufts USDA Cork Kennedy, 1996-04-22; MS247.001.004.00002.00009 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960422-A to 960422-G
    - Jeremy Merrin's South Amer. Art documented at Arts Expos, 1996-07-10; MS247.001.004.00002.00010 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960710
      Jeremy Merrin
    - Tufts Dental Awards Luncheon, 1996-05-15; MS247.001.004.00002.00011 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960515-A to 960515-C
    - Tufts: Medical Reception at DiBiaggio House, 1996-02-06; MS247.001.004.00002.00012 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960206-A to 960206-E
      School of Medicine; Elizabeth Flannagan
    - Reception for Admitted Students, 1996-04-16; MS247.001.004.00002.00013 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960416-Y to 960416-Z
    - Yankee Dental Congress, 1996-01-26; MS247.001.004.00002.00014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960126-A to 960126-L
    - Tufts Dental Catalog, 1996-04-24; MS247.001.004.00002.00015 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960424-A to 960424-G
    - Tufts Chase Gym, 1996-10-19; MS247.001.004.00002.00016 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      961019-A to 961019-E
    - Tufts Dental Alumni Weekend, 1996-04-27; MS247.001.004.00002.00017 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960427-A to 960427-R
    - Tufts Dental / Lonnie Norris Breakfast, 1996-04-27; MS247.001.004.00002.00018 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960427-Y to 960427-Z
    - Sackler Catalog, 1996-06-25; MS247.001.004.00002.00019 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960625-A to 960625-E
    - Tufts Catering, 1996-03-28; MS247.001.004.00002.00020 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      960328-A to 960328-M
  - Tufts 1997, MS247.001.004.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Tisch Library Web site virtual tour, 1997-05-03; MS247.001.004.00003.00001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      970503-A to 970503-N
    - Sackler School, 1997-07-29; MS247.001.004.00003.00002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      970729-A to 970729-G
    - The Orthodox Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew, I, 1997-10-29; MS247.001.004.00003.00003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      971029-A to 971029-P
    - Tufts: Neubauer Chair, 1995-10-17; MS247.001.004.00003.00004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      951017-A to 951017-E
    - Honorary Degree Dinner Gifford House, 1997-05-17; MS247.001.004.00003.00005 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      970517-A to 970517-G
      Kate Ryan
    - Family Reception Ballou Hall, 1997-05-17; MS247.001.004.00003.00006 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      970517-H to 970517-V
    - Robing and Post Commencement Luncheon, 1997-05-19; MS247.001.004.00003.00007 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      970519-A to 970519-H
    - Tufts: Medical Reunion / Parade O Dox, 1997-05-10; MS247.001.004.00003.00008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      970510-A to 970510-O
    - Dental Reunion, 1997-05-02; MS247.001.004.00003.00009 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      970502-A to 970502-Z
    - Chemistry Boys, 1997; MS247.001.004.00003.00010 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Walt, Robat
    - Kurt Viermetz JP Morgan, 1997-02-07; MS247.001.004.00003.00011 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      970207-A to 970207-B
    - Kurt Viermetz JP Morgan, 1997-02-07; MS247.001.004.00003.00012 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tufts 1996-1997, MS247.001.004.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Askinas, 1997-06-19; MS247.001.004.00004.00001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970619-A to 970619-E
      negatives (photographs)
    - Tufts Med Dr Norm Stearns at Silverman's, 1997-03-28; MS247.001.004.00004.00002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970328-A to 970328-D
    - Tufts: Chemistry / Utz, 1997-10-15; MS247.001.004.00004.00003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971015-A to 971015-I
      negatives (photographs); Medford Campus
    - Sackler / Medical Graduation, 1997-05-18; MS247.001.004.00004.00004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970518-A to 970518-J
    - Dental Reunion, 1997-05-02; MS247.001.004.00004.00005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970502
      negatives (photographs); Boston Campus
    - Harrington Oncology/ Tufts Vet, 1997-06-02; MS247.001.004.00004.00006 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970602-A to 970602-D
      negatives (photographs); Grafton Campus
    - Tufts Chem, 1997-11-19; MS247.001.004.00004.00007 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971119-A to 971119-C
      Al Robat; Janice Silva
    - Sam Kounaves Chem: Janice Silva, 1997-11-25; MS247.001.004.00004.00008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971125-A to 971125-D
      Sam Kounaves; Janice Silva
    - Mr. Jiaravanon & the Charden Pokphand Group, 1997-12-02; MS247.001.004.00004.00009 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971202-A to 971202-F
    - India's 50th Anniversary of Independence solo, 1997-10-03; MS247.001.004.00004.00010 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971003
    - Tufts Dental Wide Open, 1997-10-06; MS247.001.004.00004.00011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971006-A to 971006-H
    - Tufts/ Emerson Med degree ceremony at College Club, 1997-05-16; MS247.001.004.00004.00012 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970516-A to 970516-F
    - Trattoria Il Panino, 1997-05-13; MS247.001.004.00004.00013 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970513-A to 970513-D
    - Admit Reception, 1997-04-17; MS247.001.004.00004.00014 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970417-Y to 970417-Z
    - Admit Reception, 1997-04-17; MS247.001.004.00004.00015 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Shapiro Awards, 1997-04-17; MS247.001.004.00004.00016 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970417-A to 970417-D
    - Medical Alumni Senior Awards Banquet, 1997-05-14; MS247.001.004.00004.00017 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970514-A to 970514-G
    - Dental catalog post doc, 1997-04-03; MS247.001.004.00004.00018 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970403-A to 9707403-E
    - Tufts Faculty Recognition, 1997-05-29; MS247.001.004.00004.00019 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970529-A to 970529-F
    - Quick Honorary Cong. John Porter, 1997-03-10; MS247.001.004.00004.00020 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970310-A to 970310-G
    - Tufts: Joe Byrne retires, 1997-11-17; MS247.001.004.00004.00021 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971117-A to 971117-J
    - Dental Family Day/Gonthier cert & Dean's Christmas card, 1997-09-12; MS247.001.004.00004.00022 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970912-A to 970912-J
    - CROP @Meridien, 1997-02-23; MS247.001.004.00004.00023 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970223-A to 970223-N
    - CROP @Meridien, 1997-02-23; MS247.001.004.00004.00024 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Bio brochure, 1997-10-20; MS247.001.004.00004.00025 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971020-A to 971020-D
    - Tufts Jaharis @ Ritz, 1997-11-01; MS247.001.004.00004.00026 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971101-A to 971101-F
    - Sackler Lou's Fete GNA Chair, 1997-09-30; MS247.001.004.00004.00027 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970930-A to 970930-I
    - Tufts Dental Maria Papageorge Facial Surgery, 1997-08-05; MS247.001.004.00004.00028 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970805-A to 970805-C
    - Tufts Feinstein Famine, 1997-03-07; MS247.001.004.00004.00029 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970307-A to 970307-G
    - Yankee Dental, 1997-01-24; MS247.001.004.00004.00030 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970124-A to 970124-F
    - Yankee Dental, 1997-01-24; MS247.001.004.00004.00031 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Dining Services pizza, Brown & Brew, fast food, 1997-04-04; MS247.001.004.00004.00032 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970404-A to 970404-E
    - Dental The Brehms solo, 1996-05-20; MS247.001.004.00004.00033 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      960520
    - Tufts Public Health Communications, 1997-02-11; MS247.001.004.00004.00034 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970211-A to 970211-G
    - Parents Weekend at Tufts, 1997-10-18; MS247.001.004.00004.00035 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971018-A to 971018-N
    - Vet Comeback, 1997-09-06; MS247.001.004.00004.00036 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      970906-A to 970906-I
    - Health Sciences Dinner Dance at MFA, 1997-10-25; MS247.001.004.00004.00037 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971025-A to 971025-H
    - Arts & Sciences @ MFA Picasso, 1997-11-02; MS247.001.004.00004.00038 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      971102-A to 971102-F
  - Tufts 1999, MS247.001.004.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Gantcher Opening, 1999-11-05; MS247.001.004.00005.00001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      971105-A to 971105-U
      Bernie Gordon
    - Hank Azaria/ Eden White Light on the Hill, 1999-11-16; MS247.001.004.00005.00002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      991116-A to 971116-I
    - Julie Lampie Food, 1999-04-21; MS247.001.004.00005.00003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990421-A to 990421-E
    - Tufts Phonathon, 1999-11-10; MS247.001.004.00005.00004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      991110-A to 991110-B
    - Tufts: Oneal Outar's Phonathon, 1999-05-16; MS247.001.004.00005.00005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990516-A to 990516-B
    - Tufts Yankee Dental, 1999-01-22; MS247.001.004.00005.00006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990122-A to 990122-F
    - Tufts: John Holmes Poetry Walk, 1999-09-17; MS247.001.004.00005.00007 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990917-A to 990917-F
    - Tufts: Dukakis Christopher Columbus Award, 1999-10-06; MS247.001.004.00005.00008 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      991006-A to 991006-E
    - Signer Id's NEBHE, 1999-10-18; MS247.001.004.00005.00009 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      991018-A to 991018-E
    - Tufts Stern Chair, 1999-12-02; MS247.001.004.00005.00010 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      991202-A to 991202-H
    - Jaharis Medical Building Opening, 1999-04-29; MS247.001.004.00005.00011 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990429-A to 990429-L
    - Tufts: Simpson Vet Chair ( Equine Med), 1999-05-06; MS247.001.004.00005.00012 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990506-A to 990506-H
    - Honorary Degree Dinner Gifford House, 1999-05-22; MS247.001.004.00005.00013 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990522-A to 990522-F
    - Baccaleaureate, 1999-05-22; MS247.001.004.00005.00014 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990522-G to 990522-I
    - Dental Awards Luncheon, 1999-05-22; MS247.001.004.00005.00015 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990522-J to 990522-O
    - Commencement, 1999-05-23; MS247.001.004.00005.00016 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      990523-A to 990523-Q
  - Tufts 1999 Volume 2, MS247.001.004.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - University Service, 1999-05-05; MS247.001.004.00006.00001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990505-A to 990505-D
    - Tufts Chaplains, 1999-09-27; MS247.001.004.00006.00002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990927-A to 990927-C
    - International Student Graduation, 1999-11-19; MS247.001.004.00006.00003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      991119-A to 991119-F
    - Tufts Dental Alumni Weekend, 1999-05-01; MS247.001.004.00006.00004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990501-A to 990501-X
    - Tufts Parents Weekend, 1999-10-16; MS247.001.004.00006.00005 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      991016-A to 991016-N
    - Global Crime Corruption, 1999-03-05; MS247.001.004.00006.00006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990305-A to 990305-D
      Sherman Teichman
    - Fletcher: Rule of Law in South America, 1999-04-15; MS247.001.004.00006.00007 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990415-A to 990415-B
      Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Nicole Hales; Anthony Perrera
    - Tufts Vet School Comeback, 1999-09-18; MS247.001.004.00006.00008 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990918-A to 990918-I
    - Tufts: Fletcher Neil Allen & Wife Term chair, 1999-01-25; MS247.001.004.00006.00009 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990125-A to 990125-H
      Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Neil Allen
    - Tufts Dental Research Awards, 1999-05-24; MS247.001.004.00006.00010 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990524-A to 990524-C, 990524-X to 990524-Z
      Donna Hawkins; Robin Glover
    - Tufts: Rocky's Retirement, 1999-04-28; MS247.001.004.00006.00011 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990428-A to 990428-E
      Rocky Carzo
    - Charles Tufts Society Luncheon / Pops, 1999-05-20; MS247.001.004.00006.00012 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990520-A to 990520-I
    - Tufts Chinese American Studies Dinner @ Gifford House, 1999-02-25; MS247.001.004.00006.00013 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990225-A to 990225-C
      Mel Berstein; Jack Galvin
    - Dental Wide Open, 1999-10-04; MS247.001.004.00006.00014 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      991004-A to 991004-H
    - Shapiro Awards, 1999-04-22; MS247.001.004.00006.00015 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990422-A to 990422-D
    - Medical Student Awards, 1999-05-19; MS247.001.004.00006.00016 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990519-A to 990519-I
    - Tufts: Oral Surgery Grad @ Pier 4, 1999-06-14; MS247.001.004.00006.00017 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990614-A to 990614-D
    - Ted Randall Tufts, 1999-11-01; MS247.001.004.00006.00018 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      991101-A to 991101-D
      Ted Randall
    - Tufts Faculty Recognition, 1999-06-18; MS247.001.004.00006.00019 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990618-A to 990618-D
    - Tufts Music for Development, 1999-12-09; MS247.001.004.00006.00020 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      991209-A to 991209-B
      Elaine Brzycki
    - Tufts Parents Reception, 1999-04-13; MS247.001.004.00006.00021 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990413-A to 990413-C
    - Tufts Overseers and Trustees, 1999-11-04; MS247.001.004.00006.00022 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      991104-A to 991104-S
      Linda Chamberlain
    - Tufts: Medical Reunion, 1999-06-04; MS247.001.004.00006.00023 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      990604-A to 990604-P
  - Tufts 1998-2000, MS247.001.004.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Urban & Enviromental Policy @ Tufts, 1998-11-13; MS247.001.004.00007.00001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      981113-A to 981113-H
    - Tufts 98 Yankee Dental, 1998-01-17; MS247.001.004.00007.00002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      980117-A to 980117-J
    - Chas Francis Adams Raytheon Chair Dinner, 1998-03-25; MS247.001.004.00007.00003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      980325-A to 980325-E
    - Tufts Fletcher Chris Patten, 1998-09-22; MS247.001.004.00007.00004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      980922-A to 980922-B
    - Tufts Fletcher Chris Patten, 1998-09-22; MS247.001.004.00007.00005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Health Sciences MFA, 1998-05-08; MS247.001.004.00007.00006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      980508-A to 980508-W
    - Tufts Health Sciences Dinner Dance Park Plaza, 1998-10-24; MS247.001.004.00007.00007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      981024-A to 981024-L
    - Tufts Vet Comeback, 1998-09-12; MS247.001.004.00007.00008 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      980912-A to 980912-J
    - Tufts Leir Chair Dedication, 2000-12-07; MS247.001.004.00007.00009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      001207-A to 001207-G
    - Tufts: Bergstrom Chair- Lerner Lecture, 2000-04-11; MS247.001.004.00007.00010 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      000411-A to 000411-L
      Richard Lerner; Ann Esterbrooks
    - Tufts Fletcher Small States Conference, 2000-04-01; MS247.001.004.00007.00011 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      000401-A to 000401-E
    - Pre Commencement, 2000-05-20; MS247.001.004.00007.00012 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      000520-A to 000520-E
    - Baccaleaureate, 2000-05-20; MS247.001.004.00007.00013 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      000520-F to 000520-I
    - Honorary Degree Dinner, 2000-05-20; MS247.001.004.00007.00014 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      000520-J to 000520-R
    - Graduate Student Awards Coolidge Room, 2000-05-01; MS247.001.004.00007.00015 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      000501-A to 000501-C
    - Charles Tufts Society, 2000-05-18; MS247.001.004.00007.00016 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      000518-A to 000518-L
  - Tufts 1998, MS247.001.005.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Tufts: Arts & Sciences Dinner Dance, 1998-11-07; MS247.001.005.00001.00001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981107-A to 981107-H
    - Fares Lectures George Mitchell, 1998-11-04; MS247.001.005.00001.00002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981104-A to 981104-M
    - Tufts Medical / Zuuker Chair Itzak Perlman, 1998-05-06; MS247.001.005.00001.00003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980506-A to 980506-L
    - Honorary Degree Dinner (unveiling DiBiaggio portrait), 1998-05-14; MS247.001.005.00001.00004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980514-A to 980514-N
    - Tufts Sackler Medical Commencement w/robing & lunch, 1998-05-17; MS247.001.005.00001.00005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980517-A to 980517-M
    - Tufts: Dedication of Davis Square T Stop sign, 1998-10-06; MS247.001.005.00001.00006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981006-A to 981006-B
    - Tufts: Hummingbird Key, 1998-06-29; MS247.001.005.00001.00007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980629-A to 980629-E
      George Elmore; Van Bernard; Ring Drauaner
    - Solo Mim Nelson Book Dedication, 1998-10-30; MS247.001.005.00001.00008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981030
      Mim Nelson
    - Tufts Dining Brown and Brew, 1998-04-01; MS247.001.005.00001.00009 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980401-A to 980401-E
    - Tufts Dental Parents, 1998-10-10; MS247.001.005.00001.00010 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981010-A to 981010-C
    - Tufts: Berger & Son solo, 1998-12-04; MS247.001.005.00001.00011 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981204
    - Tufts Post Grad Prosthedontics, 1998-07-24; MS247.001.005.00001.00012 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980724-A to 980724-E
    - Tufts Catering Photoshoot, 1998-04-23; MS247.001.005.00001.00013 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980423-A to 980423-B
    - Tufts HNRC Signing, 1998-10-01; MS247.001.005.00001.00014 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981001-X to 981001-Z
    - Tufts V12-NROTC Memorial Dedication, 1998-09-19; MS247.001.005.00001.00015 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980919-A to 980919-H
    - Tufts Mel Bernstein, 1998-02-13; MS247.001.005.00001.00016 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980213-A to 980213-D
    - Tufts Parents Weekend, 1998-10-17; MS247.001.005.00001.00017 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981017-A to 981017-O
    - Dr Norm Stearns, 1998-02-03; MS247.001.005.00001.00018 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980203-A to 980203-B
    - Tufts: Special Programs Graduation, 1998-05-15; MS247.001.005.00001.00019 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980515-V to 980515-Y
    - Tufts, 1998-05-14; MS247.001.005.00001.00020 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980514-Y to 980514-Z
    - Tufts Gantcher Gym ground breaking, 1998-11-06; MS247.001.005.00001.00021 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981106-A to 981106-K
    - Tufts Dental Reunion, 1998-05-02; MS247.001.005.00001.00022 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980502-A to 980502-Y
    - Tufts: Goldberg Seminar Lincoln Filene Center, 1998-07-09; MS247.001.005.00001.00023 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980709-A to 980709-J
    - Tufts Faculty Recognition Dinner, 1998-06-01; MS247.001.005.00001.00024 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980601-A to 980601-E
    - John Field Retires Nutrition, 1998-06-01; MS247.001.005.00001.00025 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980601-X to 980601-Z
    - Mark Gonthier Awards / Ellie Short parents, 1998-05-16; MS247.001.005.00001.00026 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980516-A to 980516-D
    - Tufts: Delores Asher Medical Lunch, 1998-10-01; MS247.001.005.00001.00027 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981001-A to 981001-B
    - 2nd NEMC reception, 1998-04-28; MS247.001.005.00001.00028 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      980428-A to 980428-B
    - Tufts: Duranian Dental Museum Dedication, 1998-10-29; MS247.001.005.00001.00029 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981029-A to 981029-E
    - Tufts: Christopher Columbus Award, 1998-10-07; MS247.001.005.00001.00030 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981007-A to 981007-D
    - Tufts: Dental International Students Graduation, 1998-11-20; MS247.001.005.00001.00031 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      981120-A to 981120-E
  - Tufts 2000, MS247.001.005.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Tufts: Kay McCarthy Lecture in Cabot solo, 2000-11-13; MS247.001.005.00002.00001 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001113 solo
    - Tufts: Christopher Columbus Award, 2000-10-03; MS247.001.005.00002.00002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001003-A to 001003-C
    - Sackler 20th Anniversary, 2000-11-11; MS247.001.005.00002.00003 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001111-A to 001111-J
    - Tufts Dental Sellers Retires, 2000-09-11; MS247.001.005.00002.00004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000911-A to 000911-B
      School of Dental Medicine; Bill Sellers
    - Tufts V12 for Ellie Short, 2000-10-18; MS247.001.005.00002.00005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001018-A to 001018-C
    - Senior Awards Dinner Medical School, 2000-05-17; MS247.001.005.00002.00006 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000517-A to 000517-F
    - Tufts: Baronian Jumbo Awards, 2000-04-07; MS247.001.005.00002.00007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000407-A to 000407-D
    - Tufts: Jonathan Wilson reading @ Tisch solo, 2000-10-05; MS247.001.005.00002.00008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001005 solo
      Jeff Winey
    - Tufts: Dowling Hall Opening Dedication, 2000-10-12; MS247.001.005.00002.00009 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001012-A to 001012-K
    - Tufts Dental 2000 Wide Open, 2000-10-02; MS247.001.005.00002.00010 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001002-A to 001002-I
    - Tufts Parents Weekend, 2000-10-14; MS247.001.005.00002.00011 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001014-A to 001014-N
    - Tufts Dental Reunion, 2000-05-06; MS247.001.005.00002.00012 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000506-A to 000506-X
    - Tufts Composer's 60th bday Mark Devoto Reception, 2000-01-23; MS247.001.005.00002.00013 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000123-A to 000123-E
    - Tufts: Athletic Overseers: O'Neil retire board shot, 2000-04-13; MS247.001.005.00002.00014 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000413-A to 000413-B
    - Tufts Dowling Hall naming Opportunities, 2000-07-30; MS247.001.005.00002.00015 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000730-A to 000730-F
    - Tufts Dowling Hall naming Opportunities, 2000-07-30; MS247.001.005.00002.00016 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Tufts Food Julie Lampie Taco Shoot, 2000-04-10; MS247.001.005.00002.00017 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000410 solo
      Julie Lampie
    - Tufts food strawberries, 2000-05-03; MS247.001.005.00002.00018 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000503-A to 000503-B
    - Tufts: Vet Reunion in Boston 1st @ Colonade Hotel, 2000-10-11; MS247.001.005.00002.00019 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001011-A to 001011-D
    - Tufts: Fares Lecture Colin Powell, 2000-11-02; MS247.001.005.00002.00020 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001102-A to 001102-P
    - Tufts College of Citizenship & Public Service Declaration, 2000-04-21; MS247.001.005.00002.00021 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000421-A to 000421-E
      Pierre Omidyar; Pam Omidyar
    - Tufts Dental Students of Color, 2000-05-11; MS247.001.005.00002.00022 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000511-A to 000511-D
    - Tufts Medical 1st Gordon Lecture, 2000-04-14; MS247.001.005.00002.00023 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000414-A to 000414-D
      Kathleen Kruger
    - Tufts: Light on the Hill Award, 2000-11-22; MS247.001.005.00002.00024 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      001122-A to 001122-G
    - Love Canal: Gibbs Millionth Book, 2000-04-06; MS247.001.005.00002.00025 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000406-A to 000406-D
    - Tufts: Presidents Awards- Community Service, 2000-03-31; MS247.001.005.00002.00026 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000331-A to 000331-D
    - Dental Mentors w/ merit aid, 2000-03-31; MS247.001.005.00002.00027 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000331-Y to 000331-Z
    - Tufts Walt & Chemistry Students, 2000-04-13; MS247.001.005.00002.00028 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000413-X to 000413-Z
    - Tufts 1st Big community service meeting, 2000-02-10; MS247.001.005.00002.00029 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000210-A to 000210-D
    - Tufts: Dental Senior Awards, 2000-05-15; MS247.001.005.00002.00030 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000515-A to 000515-E
    - Bates Andrews Research Dinner, 2000-05-15; MS247.001.005.00002.00031 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000515-F to 000515-I
    - Tufts: Robing Commencement, 2000-05-21; MS247.001.005.00002.00032 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000521-A to 000521-I
    - Sackler Medical Commencement, 2000-05-21; MS247.001.005.00002.00033 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      000521-J to 000521-O
    - Admitted Student Reception, 2000-04-12; MS247.001.005.00002.00034 (Box 5, Folder 2)